the first two things we will want to automate are
silicon and plastic
we can start with the more streamlined one silicon
which can easily be produced with a simple chain of machines
with no input at all
the first part of this chain is rather easy
so we can just skip to the last step
the issue with that step is that
an addition of magnesium is required
it will be given back in form of magnesia
which has to be sorted out from silicon
and electrolyzed to get magnesium back
to sort apart those items
we can use drawers or barrels
and lock the item we want to sort out
once we have isolated the dust we wanted to reprocess
we can use conveyor to import it inside our electrolyzer
with that we have finished the logistic part of producing silicon
now let's see the power part
the main power sink here is the arc furnace
with its 3 amps of MV power
however that consumption will last just 1 second
and will yield the two outputs
this will cause an interesting effect
which we'll be using but I do not advise
when a machine runs out of power
it will halt for a little bit
and fill up its internal buffer before trying again
and this recipe is quick enough to be run even without a proper power source
furthermore, this machine is not going to work constantly
but it's going to have to wait for the slower ones in this chain
which means it's going to use a constant average of 32 EU per tick
that doesn't mean it can be powered with LV power
but it allows us to power everything in this chain with just a single MV turbine
finally we add two more chemical reactors
to refine our silicon to solar grade
next we have to make polyethylene
the main issue here is deciding in which way
we can either set up a new farm for the plant way
or set up a pump and refine some oil
the plant way is more renewable
but oil is more synthetically interesting
so we will be seeing the oil way
after setting up a pump over a deposit
we move the oil to our base using a long distance fluid pipeline
the first step will be to distill our oil
and here we'll already start to get lost between all of the recipes in the distillery page
a better way to deal with all of those recipes is to instead look at the distillation tower recipes
while we can't craft that machine yet
the outputs are in most of the cases the same
the circuit required in the distillery represents the layer at which the fluid will come out of the tower
and yes by using a single block we will be losing all of the fluids outside of the chosen one
the issue is now deciding which fluid we want to keep
and things quickly get convoluted
because to make plastic each one of those fluids can be working a slightly different way to get different ratios in a second distillation process
anyways we start by moving the oil into a distillery
and then we select one fluid
this fluid will have some sulfur impurities
which must be removed with the help of some hydrogen in a chemical reactor
the main issue here is that one of the two fluids must be provided through cells
to help with that we can use some GregTech tanks
we pump in the fluid, add some cells
and then apply a conveyor belt to move the filled cells
this particular recipe will output two differently filled cells
for now we have to either manually manage those
or use the drawer trick
the next step is similar, but easier to loop
since it consists of just moving back and forth a cell to refill it
as before
we will have a tank to refill the cells
which are then pushed into the adjacent chemical reactor with a conveyor belt
but this time
we will also have a conveyor on the reactor to push back empty cells
however those conveyors will block each other
unless we select the allow input setting
and with that we have severely cracked refinery gas
one of the 12 different routes of making ethylene from oil
finally we add oxygen to obtain polyethylene
this process uses a little bit of hydrogen
and a huge amount of oxygen
to get the hydrogen we are electrolyzing water
and while this process makes some oxygen too
it's far from our requirements
the easiest way to make all of that oxygen
is to just use the waste one from our silicon processing
one other thing you could want to automate is ore processing
here we have an example of that
made using steam and logistic pipes
let's see how it works
in this test we drop all of the minerals we dig
if those are already sorted out
they will be moved to the machine we have designed for the next processing step
in this example
we are setting the destination filters with item sink modules
and extracting materials from the outputs with unfiltered extractor modules
every time we will be inserting a new ore
it will stick in the starting chest
that will be the signal that we have to decide how to process it
to do that we can use NEI bookmarks to Mark the path we decide
then we apply those bookmarks to the cards of the correct machines
another thing is that until we get into HV
we can't get the useful byproduct of the HV macerator
so we should be careful of what we process until then
on the opposite side
sometimes some useless byproduct processing is going to clog things up
to speed up things and save some energy
we can use some different machines
to finish off, I'd like to remind you that
you can quickly restrict flow direction of a long segment of pipes by setting the wrench in line mode by crouching and clicking on air
and for today that's it
bye bye
我们想要自动化的前两件事是
硅粉和塑料
我们可以从更线性的硅粉开始
它可以很容易地用简单的机器链生产
而几乎不需要输入
这条链的第一部分相当简单
所以我们可以跳到最后一步
这一步的问题是
需要额外添加镁
它将以氧化镁的形式返还
我们需要把它产物从硅中分离出来
并电解以取回镁
要分类产物
我们可以用抽屉或桶
并锁定我们要整理的物品
一旦我们分离了想要重新处理的粉
我们可以使用传送带将其导入电解机内
这样我们就完成了生产硅粉的物流部分
现在让我们看看电力部分
这里的主要用电器是电弧炉
它要用 3A MV
然而，耗电仅持续1秒
并将产生两个输出
这会引起有趣的效果
我们将使用它，但我不建议这样做
当机器没电时
它会停一会儿
并在再次尝试之前填满其内部缓冲区
这个配方足够快，即使没有合适的电源也能运行
此外，这台机器不会一直工作
因为它必须等待这个链条中较慢的那些
这意味着它平均来说，将使用 32 EU/t
这并不意味着它可以用LV电源供电。
但它允许我们用一个MV涡轮机
为这个产线中的所有东西供电
最后我们再加两个化学反应釜
将我们的硅提炼成太阳能级硅
接下来我们要做聚乙烯
这里的主要问题是决定以哪种方式生产
我们可以建立一个新的农场，用植物来生产
或者建立一个泵并提炼石油
植物方式更具可再生性
但是石油综合来说更有趣
所以我们会看到石油产线
在油泉上安装泵后
我们用长距离输油管道把石油运到基地
第一步是提炼石油
在这里，我们已经在蒸馏页面的所有配方之间晕头转向了
处理所有这些配方的更好方法是查看蒸馏塔配方
虽然我们还不能制造那台机器
在大多数情况下，输出是相同的
小蒸馏所需的电路代表了蒸馏塔的流体产出层
是的，通过使用单方块
我们将失去所选层之外的所有液体
现在的问题是决定我们要保留哪种液体
事情很快就会变得复杂
因为要制造塑料，每种液体都可以以稍微不同的方式
在第二道蒸馏工序中获得不同的产率
不管怎样，我们从把石油搬进小蒸馏开始
然后我们选择一种流体
这种液体会有一些硫杂质
必须在化学反应釜中借助氢移除
这里的主要问题是两种液体中的一种必须通过单元提供
为了解决这个问题，我们可以使用GT缸
我们注入液体，加入一些空单元
然后使用传送带移动填满的单元
此特定配方将输出两个不同填充的单元
现在我们要么手动管理这些
或者使用抽屉技巧
下一步类似，但更容易循环
因为它只包括来回移动一个单元来重新填充它
和以前一样
我们用一个缸来装满单元
然后用传送带将其输入相邻的化学反应器
但这一次
我们还将在反应釜上安装传送带，将空单元推回
然而，这些传送带会相互阻挡
除非我们选择允许输入
这样我们就有了重度裂化的炼油气
石油制乙烯的12种不同方法之一
最后我们加入氧气得到聚乙烯
这个过程需要一点氢气
和大量的氧气
为了得到氢，我们电解水
虽然这个过程也会产生一些氧气
这与我们的要求相差甚远
制造所有氧气的最简单方法
就是用我们硅加工的废料
你可能想要自动化的另一件事是矿石处理
这里我们有一个例子
使用蒸汽和物流管道制造
让我们看看它是如何工作的
在这个测试中，我们放入挖掘的所有矿物
如果这些已经被标记过了
它们将被转移到我们为下一步加工设计的机器上
在这个例子中
我们正在使用物品收纳模块设置目标过滤器
并使用未经过滤的提取模块从输出中提取材料
每次我们都会放入新矿石
它会一直呆在初始箱子里
这将是我们必须决定如何处理它的信号
为此，我们可以使用NEI书签来标记我们决定的路径
然后我们将这些书签应用到正确机器的模块上
另一件事是在我们进入HV之前
我们无法得到HV研磨机的有用副产品
所以在那之前我们应该注意我们处理的东西
在另一边
有时一些无用的副产品加工会堵塞东西
为了加快速度并节省一些电量
我们可以使用一些不同的机器
最后，我想提醒你
你可以通过蹲下并单击空气将扳手设置为直线模式
来快速限制长管道的流动方向
今天就这样了
拜拜